http://www.elitetraining.co.uk/about-us/privacy-policy-2

.
.
AboutAvailability and CostsOur ConsultantsCustomersElite BlogsFAQsBusiness TrainingIce Breakers - Team MeetingsManagement GamesTeam ActivitiesTeam Building GamesTeam Building ExercisesTeam Building Games for WorkTraining GamesTraining MaterialsWill you run the game for me?What is a Business Game?What Skills are Involved?What levels of knowledge and experience can a business strategy game cover?Is the training transferable to the workplace?If I buy a game how do I run it?What remote L&D does Elite provide?What do your L&D Programmes involveWhat apprenticeship standards do you run?What is Off The Job (OTJ) Training?What is the apprenticeship levy?Mission StatementNewsOrdering a GamePrivacy PolicyTerms Conditions and LegalBusiness GamesAll Games Listed by TypeAll Games Listed by NameOrdering a Game - InformationAnalysis Crime SquadGlobal TradingIn-TrayRunning Your Business for ProfitSafari Park Sales ChallengeAssessment and RecruitingBrand New Business - Creative SalesBuilding The BridgeColourblind ColourshapesCrime SquadCustomer Service ChallengeCustomer Service DecisionsDisplay Shelf Get Your Message AcrossIn-TrayLife's ChoicesManager & Supervisor Role & SkillsRunning Your Business for ProfitRoller Coaster BallSales & Negotiation (North Pole)Survival by TeamworkTeam ShapesWe Can Do Company Business SimulationBrand New Business - Creative SalesGlobal TradingIn-TrayManager & Supervisor Role & Skills
Running Your Business for ProfitSafari Park Sales Challenge Sales & Negotiation (North Pole) We Can Do CompanyChange ManagementIn-TrayRunning Your Business For ProfitSafari Park Sales Challenge
We Can Do CompanyCoachingPractical Coaching Manager & Supervisor Role & Skills Life's ChoicesCommercial ThinkingBrand New Business - Creative SalesCustomer Service ChallengeCustomer Service DecisionsIn-Tray Running Your Business for ProfitSafari Park Sales Challenge Sales & Negotiation (North Pole)We Can Do CompanyCommunicationBrand New Business - Creative SalesBuilding the BridgeCoaching Practical
Colourblind I Colourblind II ColourshapesContinuous ImprovementsCrime SquadCustomer Service ChallengeCustomer Service DecisionsDisplay ShelfGet Your Message Across Global TradingManager & Supervisor Role & Skills Mentoring PracticalMinefieldRoller Coaster BallRoller Coaster BallRunning Your Business for ProfitSales & Negotiation (North Pole)Survival by TeamworkSafari Park Sales Challenge Team ShapesTreasure of Pirate IslandWe Can Do CompanyConference, Seminar or EventBrand New Business - Creative SalesBuilding The Bridge Colourblind I ColourshapesContinuous ImprovementCreative Business CompanyCrime SquadCustomer Service ChallengeCustomer Service DecisionsDisplay ShelfElectric FenceGet Your Message AcrossGlobal TradingHelium StickMinefieldPipelineRoller Coaster BallRunning Your Business for ProfitSales & Negotiation (North Pole)Safari Park Sales Challenge Survival by TeamworkTeam ShapesTreasure of Pirate IslandWe Can Do CompanyConflict ManagementColourblind IColourshapesCreative Business CompanyGet Your Message AcrossSales & Negotiation (North Pole) Survival by Teamwork Treasure of Pirate IslandWe Can Do CompanyConstruction GamesBuilding the BridgeDisplay Shelf Roller Coaster BallContinuous & Process ImprovementBrand New Business - Creative Sales Continuous ImprovementCustomer Service Challenge Display ShelfGlobal TradingMinefieldRunning Your Business for ProfitCreative Thinking Brand New Business - Creative SalesBuilding The Bridge Creative Business CompanyCustomer Service ChallengeRoller Coaster BallSales & Negotiation (North Pole)Treasure of Pirate IslandWe Can Do CompanyCustomer ServiceBrand New Business - Creative Sales Customer Service Challenge Customer Service DecisionsIn-TrayPipelineRunning Your Business for ProfitSales & Negotiation (North Pole)Finance in Business Global Trading Running Your Business for ProfitSafari Park Sales Challenge Global ThinkingGlobal TradingHuman ResourcesIn-TrayManager & Supervisor Role & Skills Running Your Business for ProfitIce Breakers and EnergisersBuilding The BridgeColourshapesContinuous Improvement Creative Business CompanyElectric Fence Helium StickLife's ChoicesMinefieldPipelineRoller Coaster BallSurvival by TeamworkTeam ShapesInterface Management Roller Coaster BallRunning Your Business for ProfitWe Can Do CompanyLeadership and ManagementBuilding The BridgeContinuous ImprovementCrime SquadCustomer Service DecisionsDisplay ShelfGlobal TradingIn-Tray Manager & Supervisor Role & Skills MinefieldRoller Coaster BallRunning Your Business for ProfitSales & Negotiation (North Pole)Survival by TeamworkTeam ShapesTreasure of Pirate IslandWe Can Do CompanyManaging MeetingsGet Your Message AcrossIn-TrayMentoring Practical MentoringLife's ChoicesNegotiationBrand New Business - Creative SalesColourshapesCustomer Service ChallengeCustomer Service DecisionsGlobal Trading Safari Park Sales Challenge Sales & Negotiation (North Pole) Survival by TeamworkTreasure of Pirate IslandOpenness and TrustSafari Park Sales Challenge Sales & Negotiation (North Pole) Treasure of Pirate IslandPerformance ManagementCoaching Practical Continuous ImprovementGet Your Message AcrossManager & Supervisor Role & Skills Planning & ProjectsBuilding The BridgeContinuous ImprovementDisplay ShelfGlobal TradingMinefieldRoller Coaster BallRunning Your Business for ProfitSafari Park Sales Challenge Sales & Negotiation (North Pole)Team ShapesTreasure of Pirate IslandWe Can Do CompanyPresentation SkillsBrand New Business - Creative SalesCustomer Service ChallengeRunning Your Business for Profit We Can Do CompanyProblem Solving & Decision MakingBrand New Business - Creative SalesBuilding The BridgeCoaching Practical Colourblind IColourshapesContinuous Improvement Creative Business CompanyCustomer Service ChallengeCustomer Service Decisions Crime Squad Display ShelfElectric FenceHelium StickMentoring PracticalMinefieldPipelineRoller Coaster BallRunning Your Business for Profit Team ShapesSafari Park Sales Challenge Sales & Negotiation (North Pole)Survival by TeamworkTreasure of Pirate IslandProfitabilityCustomer Service DecisionsGlobal Trading Running Your Business for ProfitSafari Park Sales Challenge Sales & Negotiation (North Pole)We Can Do CompanyRemote WorkingColourblind IColourshapesCrime SquadGet Your Message AcrossGlobal TradingRequirementsBrand New Business - Creative SalesBuilding The BridgeCrime SquadCustomer Service ChallengeRoller Coaster BallRunning Your Business for ProfitSafari Park Sales Challenge Sales & Negotiation (North Pole)Survival by TeamworkWe Can Do CompanyRisk Management Global TradingMinefieldElectric FenceSurvival by TeamworkSales & Marketing Brand New Business - Creative Sales Sales & Negotiation (North Pole) Safari Park Sales ChallengeRunning Your Business for ProfitSilo Busting Team CooperationBuilding The BridgeColourshapes Crime SquadCustomer Service DecisionsDisplay ShelfElectric FenceGet Your Message AcrossHelium StickLife's ChoicesPipelineRoller Coaster BallRunning Your Business for ProfitSafari Park Sales Challenge Sales & Negotiation (North Pole)Survival by TeamworkTeam Shapes Treasure of Pirate IslandWe Can Do CompanyStrategic Mgt & Planning Global TradingRunning Your Business for ProfitSafari Park Sales Challenge Sales & Negotiation (North Pole)Team ShapesTeamworkBrand New Business - Creative SalesBuilding The Bridge Colourblind I ColourshapesContinuous ImprovementCreative Business Company Display ShelfElectric FenceGet Your Message AcrossGlobal TradingHelium StickLife's ChoicesMinefieldPipelineRunning Your Business for ProfitRoller Coaster BallSafari Park Sales Challenge Sales & Negotiation (North Pole)Survival by Teamwork Team ShapesTreasure of Pirate IslandWe Can Do CompanyTeamwork - 40+ peopleCreativity Business CompanyCrime SquadRoller Coaster BallRunning Your Business for ProfitSurvival by TeamworkTeam ShapesTreasure of Pirate IslandTime ManagementContinuous ImprovementDisplay Shelf In-TrayRoller Coaster BallRunning Your Business for ProfitTeam ShapesWe Can Do CompanyValues Life's ChoicesManager & Supervisor Role & Skills Training CoursesAll Courses Listed by NameApprenticeship StandardsAssociate Project Manager Level 4Business Administrator Level 3HR Consultant / Partner Level 5HR Support Level 3Junior Management Consultant Level 4Operations / Departmental Manager Level 5Sales Executive Level 4Team Leader / Supervisor Level 3Dealing with Difficult PeopleConflict Resolution CourseDealing with Difficult People CourseHandling Aggression CourseGeneral Business Skills Business AnalysisBusiness FinancesCommercial AwarenessCreative ThinkingChange ManagementCustomer Service SkillsDecision MakingEquality, Diversity, Inclusion & BelongingLetter WritingManaging MeetingsMentoringMicrosoft SkillsNegotiationOperations ManagementProblem SolvingProject ManagementReport WritingReverse MentoringStressTelephone TechniquesPresentation SkillsManagement SkillsAppraisalsCoaching Skills Drugs AwarenessLeadership TrainingManaging PeoplePerformance ManagementSupervisory SkillsTrain the TrainerCorporate WellnessMarketing & SalesCopywritingDigital Marketing Marketing for Non-MarketersMarketing StrategyTelephone Sales Marketing Training Sales Management Sales Presentation Sales Training Social Media Personal DevelopmentAnger Management Assertiveness
Communications SkillsInterpersonal SkillsNeuro Linquistic ProgrammingPositive ThinkingRelationship BuildingSelf AwarenessTeam Working Skills Time ManagementTraining Games for TrainersTeam BuildingCreative Business CompanyTeam Building ActivitiesTeam ChallengesTreasure and Scavenger HuntWho Done It?CoachingOur CoachesExecutive CoachingBusiness CoachingTeam CoachingShop
About us
Privacy Policy
Elite Training European Ltd respects the privacy of visitors to this web site and is committed to making the best effort we can to safeguard your information. We will not wilfully disclose any personal information regarding our users without first obtaining their permission, unless required by law.
What Information does Elite Training European Ltd Collect?
We do not collect any personal information about you (such as your name or email address) except when you specifically and knowingly provide that information. We do keep a record of the IP addresses from which users access our site. This data is used by us for internal administration, and to analyse the way in which people use our site, so that we can keep improving the services we offer. This data also provides us with anonymous and broad demographic information about those using our site.
Email
We receive and reply to email from users on a regular basis. For record-keeping purposes we retain copies of all incoming and outgoing email. Information in the email we receive or send will not be disclosed to any third party without the permission of the sender, either express or implied, unless required by law.
Links
The Elite Training European Ltd site contains links to external sites. Please be aware that some of these external sites are developed by people over whom we have no control, and we are not responsible for their privacy practices. This Privacy Policy applies only to the Elite Training European Ltd site.
We encourage you to familiarise yourself with the privacy policy of any Web site you visit which collects personal information, and to exercise discretion when providing such information.
Cookies
When you visit one of our websites, we may send you a cookie. A cookie is a small file which is placed on your computer or device.
1. Essential Cookies
These cookies are essential for the running of our websites. Without the use of these cookies parts of our websites would not function. For example when you login to the website a session is created to allow you to browse the site and play games.  Without this session cookie you would have to login to every single page you accessed.
2. Analytical Cookies
We use these types of cookies to monitor our websites performance and how users may use it. These cookies provide us with information that helps us provide better products to our users and also to identify any areas that may need maintenance.
3. Functional Cookies
Functional cookies are used to remember your preferences on our websites. This can be anything from remembering your username or recording that you have read a site message so you don’t view it again.
How to control the use of cookies
You are not obliged to accept cookies and may modify your browser so that it will not accept cookies. The browser you use to surf the web not only allows you to see the cookies that you have got but also allows you to control their use.
You can control them by allowing them, deleting them individually or deleting all of them. You can also set your browser to not accept cookies altogether. If this option is selected, you should be aware that many websites will not function properly or at all. It may be possible to set your browser to not accept cookies and ask for your consent before each cookie is set on your device. This gives you control over what is set on your device, however has the drawback of slowing down your browsing experience.
There are different levels of control too. You are able to prevent just third party cookies being deployed, effectively opting out of behavioural advertising, and some even allow you to block specific companies you do not wish to deploy a cookie, instead of selecting all companies.
In order to manage your cookies, please select your browser from the list below and follow the instructions:
Internet Explorer
Chrome
Safari
Firefox
Opera
Mobile devices:
Android
Safari
Windows Phone
Blackberry
Changes to the Privacy Policy
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time at our discretion and without notice. If we do, an updated version of this Privacy Policy will be made available on this site so that you remain aware of the data we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Further information
Please feel free to contact us if you have any questions, comments or would like more information. You can call us on +44 (0)20 3290 1473 or send us a message.
This Privacy Statement is version 2.0, and replaces all previous versions.
More in this Section
Availability and Costs
Our Consultants
Our Customers
Elite Blog
Testimonials
FAQs
Ordering a Game
Contact Us
Liz Garrard Elite Training European Ltd 3 Parkers Place Martlesham Heath Ipswich IP5 3UX UK
Telephone: +44 (0) 20 3290 1473
Email: info@elitetraining.co.uk
Follow us
Contact
Elite Training European Ltd
Telephone: +44 (0) 20 3290 1473
Email: info@elitetraining.co.uk
Information
EliteTrainingEU
Are you ready to provide face-to-face training again for your staff? Here's @UspJones our Training Managers' take o… https://t.co/nSEDSaxJDh
Aug 10
•
reply
•
retweet
•
favorite
Mobile Menu
AboutAvailability and CostsOur ConsultantsCustomersElite BlogsFAQsBusiness TrainingIce Breakers - Team MeetingsManagement GamesTeam ActivitiesTeam Building GamesTeam Building ExercisesTeam Building Games for WorkTraining GamesTraining MaterialsWill you run the game for me?What is a Business Game?What Skills are Involved?What levels of knowledge and experience can a business strategy game cover?Is the training transferable to the workplace?If I buy a game how do I run it?What remote L&D does Elite provide?What do your L&D Programmes involveWhat apprenticeship standards do you run?What is Off The Job (OTJ) Training?What is the apprenticeship levy?Mission StatementNewsOrdering a GamePrivacy PolicyTerms Conditions and LegalBusiness GamesFinance in BusinessGlobal TradingRunning Your Business for ProfitRisk ManagementGlobal TradingMinefieldOrdering a Game - InformationAll Games Listed by TypeAssessment and RecruitingBuilding The BridgeColourshapesCreative Business CompanyCrime SquadCustomer Service DecisionsDisplay ShelfIn-TrayLife's ChoicesRunning Your Business for ProfitSupervisors & ManagementSurvival by TeamworkTeam ShapesWe Can Do CompanyBusiness SimulationCreative Business CompanyGlobal TradingRunning Your Business for ProfitWe Can Do CompanyChange ManagementWe Can Do CompanyCoachingPractical CoachingCommunicationBuilding the BridgeColourblind IColourblind IIColourshapesCrime SquadCustomer Service DecisionsDisplay ShelfGet Your Message AcrossMinefieldRoller Coaster BallSurvival by TeamworkTeam ShapesCreative ThinkingBrand New Business - Creative SalesCreative Business CompanyTreasure of Pirate IslandIce Breakers and EnergisersColourshapesCrime SquadElectric FenceHelium StickMinefieldPipelineRoller Coaster BallSurvival by TeamworkTeam ShapesLeadership and ManagementBuilding The BridgeContinuous ImprovementCustomer Service DecisionsDisplay ShelfGlobal TradingIn-TrayRunning Your Business for ProfitSupervisor & ManagementSurvival by TeamworkTeam ShapesMentoringPractical MentoringNegotiationColourshapesCustomer Service DecisionsSales & Negotiation (North Pole)Safari Park Sales ChallengeSurvival by TeamworkPlanning & ProjectsBuilding The BridgeRoller Coaster BallProblem SolvingColourshapesCreative Business CompanyCustomer Service DecisionsDisplay ShelfSurvival by TeamworkTeam ShapesTreasure of Pirate IslandTeamwork - CooperationBuilding The BridgeCrime SquadCustomer Service DecisionsLife's ChoicesPipelineRoller Coaster BallSurvival by TeamworkTreasure of Pirate IslandWe Can Do CompanyTeamworkColourshapesContinuous ImprovementCreative Business CompanyDisplay ShelfElectric FenceGlobal TradingHelium StickMinefieldRunning Your Business for ProfitSurvival by TeamworkTeam ShapesTeamwork - 40+ peopleCreativity Business CompanyCrime SquadRoller Coaster BallRunning Your Business for ProfitSurvival by TeamworkTeam ShapesTreasure of Pirate IslandCustomer ServiceCustomer Service DecisionsPipelineRunning Your Business for ProfitTime ManagementIn-TrayValuesLife's ChoicesSales & MarketingBrand New Business - Creative SalesSales & Negotiation (North Pole)Safari Park Sales ChallengeStrategic Mgt & PlanningGlobal TradingRunning Your Business for ProfitContinuous ImprovementContinuous ImprovementDisplay ShelfRunning Your Business for ProfitContinuous ImprovementTraining CoursesAll Courses Listed by NameApprenticeship StandardsAssociate Project Manager Level 4Business Administrator Level 3HR Consultant / Partner Level 5HR Support Level 3Junior Management Consultant Level 4Operations / Departmental Manager Level 5Sales Executive Level 4Team Leader / Supervisor Level 3Dealing with Difficult PeopleConflict Resolution CourseDealing with Difficult People CourseHandling Aggression CourseGeneral Business Skills Business AnalysisBusiness FinancesCommercial AwarenessCreative ThinkingChange ManagementCustomer Service SkillsDecision MakingEquality, Diversity, Inclusion & BelongingLetter WritingManaging MeetingsMentoringMicrosoft SkillsNegotiationOperations ManagementProblem SolvingProject ManagementReport WritingReverse MentoringStressTelephone TechniquesPresentation SkillsManagement SkillsAppraisalsCoaching Skills Drugs AwarenessLeadership TrainingManaging PeoplePerformance ManagementSupervisory SkillsTrain the TrainerCorporate WellnessMarketing & SalesCopywritingDigital Marketing Marketing for Non-MarketersMarketing StrategyTelephone Sales Marketing Training Sales Management Sales Presentation Sales Training Social Media Personal DevelopmentAnger Management Assertiveness
Communications SkillsInterpersonal SkillsNeuro Linquistic ProgrammingPositive ThinkingRelationship BuildingSelf AwarenessTeam Working Skills Time ManagementTraining Games for TrainersTeam BuildingCreative Business CompanyTeam Building ActivitiesTeam ChallengesTreasure and Scavenger HuntWho Done It?CoachingOur CoachesExecutive CoachingBusiness CoachingTeam CoachingShop
The cart is empty
